Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
♪Scattered fragments can't piece together the memories of the past♪
♪الشظايا المتناثرة لا يمكنها تجميع ذكريات الماضي♪
♪The movie hasn't ended, tears glimmer in my eyes♪
♪الفيلم لم ينتهي بعد، والدموع تتلألأ في عيني♪
♪Sitting alone by the street, feeling lost and hesitant♪
♪أجلس وحدي في الشارع، أشعر بالضياع والتردد♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it drift, let it dance♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تنجرف، دعها ترقص♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪همس بهدوء♪
♪The flowers that withered in my hand♪
♪الزهور التي ذبلت في يدي♪
♪Cannot call back the ones gone♪
♪لا أستطيع استدعاء من رحلوا♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it shatter, let it fade away♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تتحطم، دعها تتلاشى♪
♪Old stories like drifting dust♪
♪قصص قديمة مثل الغبار المنجرف♪
♪Letters too short for my long feelings, youth slips away♪
♪رسائل قصيرة جدًا بالنسبة لمشاعري الطويلة، الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Farewell, my dear♪
♪ وداعا يا عزيزي ♪
♪Endless pain through day and night cycles♪
♪ألم لا ينتهي خلال دورات الليل والنهار♪
♪Longing and care♪
♪الشوق والرعاية♪
=Life Like=
=مثل الحياة=
=Episode 7=
=الحلقة 7=
(Did he notice something?)
(هل لاحظ شيئا؟)
I heard Mr. Song
سمعت السيد سونغ
was assassinated by a killer that goes by "Red Bean."
تم اغتياله على يد قاتل يُدعى "الفاصوليا الحمراء".
"Red Bean"?
"الفاصوليا الحمراء"؟
The red bean that grows in southern lands?
الفاصولياء الحمراء التي تنمو في الأراضي الجنوبية؟
Your palms are sweating.
راحة يديك تتعرق.
Of course, you're gripping me so tightly.
بالطبع، أنت تمسك بي بقوة.
Who are you looking for?
من تبحث عنه؟
Good day, Mrs. Song.
يوم جيد، السيدة سونغ.
I'm Zhou Musheng from the North City Chamber of Commerce.
أنا تشو موشينغ من غرفة تجارة مدينة الشمال.
This is my friend,
هذا صديقي
Rose.
وَردَة.
I've heard of you.
لقد سمعت عنك.
I knew sooner or later
لقد عرفت عاجلا أم آجلا
someone would come looking for us.
سيأتي شخص ما يبحث عنا.
Let's talk in the room.
دعونا نتحدث في الغرفة.
Please have a seat.
من فضلك اجلس .
Serve the tea.
تقديم الشاي.
Let's not beat around the bush.
دعونا لا ندور حول الموضوع.
I'll be blunt.
سأكون صريحا.
Mrs. Song,
السيدة سونغ،
the people despise collaborators.
الشعب يحتقر المتعاونين
Mr. Song is dead.
السيد سونغ مات.
Those precious items he had
تلك الأشياء الثمينة التي كان يملكها
would be better off with someone who knows their value.
سيكون من الأفضل أن تتعامل مع شخص يعرف قيمته.
Song only collected them as a hobby.
لقد جمعها سونغ فقط كهواية.
Are you
أنت
a fellow collector?
زميل جامع؟
I don't know much about them,
لا أعرف الكثير عنهم،
but my boss is an expert.
لكن رئيسي خبير.
Why not bring out a few pieces
لماذا لا نخرج بعض القطع
for him to appraise?
لكي يقدر؟
That can be arranged.
يمكن ترتيب ذلك.
We only ask
نحن نطلب فقط
that he put in a good word for us
أنه وضع كلمة طيبة لنا
with the higher-ups.
مع كبار المسؤولين.
Song
أغنية
is dead.
لقد مات.
Can these matters
هل يمكن لهذه الأمور
end here?
تنتهي هنا؟
Leave a chance
اترك فرصة
for me and my children to survive.
من أجل بقائي أنا وأطفالي على قيد الحياة.
I don't get to decide who gets labeled a traitor.
لا أستطيع أن أقرر من هو الذي يتم تصنيفه كخائن.
But you came to the right person
ولكنك أتيت إلى الشخص المناسب
to make a plea.
لتقديم التماس.
I can try to speak for you,
يمكنني أن أحاول التحدث نيابة عنك،
depending on your course of action.
اعتمادًا على مسار عملك.
It's customary to bring gifts when meeting for the first time.
من المعتاد إحضار الهدايا عند اللقاء الأول.
Right.
يمين.
Please feel free to look around.
من فضلك لا تتردد في النظر حولك.
If anything suits you,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء يناسبك،
I'll have my people pack it up.
سأطلب من شعبي أن يحزموا أمتعتهم.
You can take your time to admire them at your leisure.
يمكنك أن تأخذ وقتك للاستمتاع بها وقتما تشاء.
We couldn't possibly.
لا يمكننا ذلك على الاطلاق.
Come, Rose.
هيا يا روز.
Take a look around. If anything catches your eye,
ألقِ نظرة حولك. إذا لفت انتباهك أي شيء،
tell Mrs. Song.
أخبر السيدة سونغ.
This, this,
هذا، هذا،
and those…
وهؤلاء…
All of these.
كل هذه.
This, that…
هذا، ذاك…
And all of these.
وكل هذا.
I'll take all of them.
سوف آخذهم جميعا.
All right.
حسنًا.
There are too many eyes during the day.
هناك الكثير من العيون خلال النهار.
I'll send someone to deliver them to your residence tonight.
سأرسل شخصًا لتسليمها إلى مقر إقامتك الليلة.
Our boss has just
رئيسنا للتو
this little hobby.
هذه الهواية الصغيرة.
Thank you, Mrs. Song.
شكرا لك سيدتي سونغ.
It's late.
إنه متأخر.
I won't keep you for dinner.
لن أبقيك على العشاء.
What's that smell?
ما هذه الرائحة؟
Those are the dogs Mr. Song kept.
هذه هي الكلاب التي كان السيد سونغ يربيها.
I found them dirty and smelly,
لقد وجدتهم قذرين ورائحتهم كريهة،
so I locked them up.
لذلك قمت بإغلاقهم.
(There's something suspicious here.)
(هناك شيء مشبوه هنا.)
You two have a safe trip.
أتمنى لكما رحلة آمنة.
Mrs. Song.
السيدة سونغ.
I'll report
سأبلغ
what you told me to the boss.
ما قلته لي للرئيس.
But if today's matter leaks,
ولكن إذا تسربت مسألة اليوم،
you'll be responsible.
ستكون مسؤولا.
It won't.
لن يحدث ذلك.
My lips are sealed.
شفتاي مغلقتان.
(Hmph.)
(همف.)
(Robbing people while looking so respectable.)
(سرقة الناس بينما يبدو محترمًا جدًا.)
(How hypocritical.)
(كم هو منافق.)
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
That traitor hoarded
لقد احتكر ذلك الخائن
many treasures.
العديد من الكنوز.
This is just the tip of the iceberg.
وهذا مجرد غيض من فيض.
This one looks nice.
هذا يبدو لطيفا.
Consider it my appearance fee.
اعتبرها رسوم حضوري.
Money grubber.
المال يتأمل.
I'm a popular singer.
أنا مغني مشهور.
I charge well.
أنا أتقاضى رسومًا جيدة.
Can you fit all of that in your purse?
هل تستطيعين وضع كل ذلك في حقيبتك؟
I'll be off, then.
سأذهب إذن.
Let me know if anything like this
أخبرني إذا كان هناك أي شيء مثل هذا
comes up again.
يظهر مرة أخرى.
You're leaving just like that?
هل ستغادر هكذا؟
What?
ماذا؟
Are you inviting me to stay the night?
هل تدعوني للبقاء ليلاً؟
Did the Song Residence
هل كانت الأغنية مقيمة؟
bring up any memories?
هل تذكر أي ذكريات؟
Not really.
ليس حقيقيًا.
But that treasure room
ولكن تلك غرفة الكنز
does seem familiar.
يبدو مألوفا.
Probably because these treasures all seem so dear to me.
ربما لأن هذه الكنوز كلها تبدو عزيزة جدًا بالنسبة لي.
If there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر،
I'm going to bed.
سأذهب إلى السرير.
Any luck
أي حظ
finding the students?
العثور على الطلاب؟
There's a traitor among the students.
هناك خائن بين الطلاب.
The mole sold
تم بيع الخلد
the students' information to Song.
معلومات الطلاب إلى سونغ.
To curry favor with the Japanese,
لكسب ود اليابانيين،
he kidnapped a bunch of them.
لقد اختطف مجموعة منهم.
Much time has passed,
لقد مر وقت طويل،
and I still haven't found where the students ended up.
ولم أجد بعد أين انتهى الطلاب.
What's that smell?
ما هذه الرائحة؟
Those are the dogs Mr. Song kept.
هذه هي الكلاب التي كان السيد سونغ يربيها.
I found them dirty and smelly,
لقد وجدتهم قذرين ورائحتهم كريهة،
so I locked them up.
لذلك قمت بإغلاقهم.
(That room.)
(تلك الغرفة.)
(The students.)
(الطلاب.)
Extra, extra!
إضافي، إضافي!
Read all about it!
قراءة كل شيء عن ذلك!
This is what I found at Mr. Song's residence.
هذا ما وجدته في منزل السيد سونغ.
These are all just names.
هذه كلها مجرد أسماء.
And a key.
ومفتاح.
(There's definitely more to that room.)
(هناك بالتأكيد المزيد في هذه الغرفة.)
(That key)
(هذا المفتاح)
(might be the key to that room.)
(قد يكون مفتاح تلك الغرفة.)
What do you want the key for?
ماذا تريد المفتاح له؟
I might know
ربما اعرف
what it's used for.
ما هو استخدامه؟
I'll test my theory tonight.
سأختبر نظريتي الليلة.
♪The world all marvels as fireworks rise♪
♪يندهش العالم كله عندما ترتفع الألعاب النارية♪
♪Magnificent like a blooming dream♪
♪رائعة مثل حلم مزدهر♪
♪Yet who sees the lingering red after the burst♪
♪ومع ذلك من يرى اللون الأحمر المتبقي بعد الانفجار♪
♪Fading into the cold night sky♪
♪تتلاشى في سماء الليل الباردة♪
♪Without the graves of blood and fire♪
♪بدون قبور الدم والنار♪
♪How could there be glory in prosperous times♪
♪كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك مجد في الأوقات المزدهرة♪
♪May that fleeting red of fireworks remain in our hearts♪
♪أتمنى أن يبقى ذلك اللون الأحمر العابر للألعاب النارية في قلوبنا♪
♪Freedom and faith engraved forever♪
♪الحرية والإيمان محفوران إلى الأبد♪
♪You and I are both in the muddy flood♪
♪أنت وأنا في الطوفان الموحل♪
♪Destined to share life and death together♪
♪مُقدَّر لنا أن نتقاسم الحياة والموت معًا♪
♪Life lights the night sky like fireworks' red♪
♪الحياة تضيء سماء الليل مثل الألعاب النارية الحمراء♪
♪Not seeking to engulf the world, just refusing mediocrity♪
♪لا أسعى إلى ابتلاع العالم، فقط أرفض الرداءة♪
♪Even if a single second is all we have in life♪
♪حتى لو كانت ثانية واحدة هي كل ما لدينا في الحياة♪
♪We must sow seeds for our ideals♪
♪علينا أن نزرع بذورًا لمُثُلنا العليا♪